BPI and several other little startups
and so I walked into this computer store
the owner looks at me and he says you
might you're you're pretty good
technically but you're you're not going
to be able to sell computers come
on you don't look you're not a Salesman
I said well give you a chance he said he
he said oh okay and I said here I'll
make a deal with you I if I sell this is
a store that probably sells maybe 100 to
$50,000 worth of computers in a year you
know and I said I'll bet you I can sell
you a million dollars worth of computers
this year and I and if I do I'll make
you a bet I I'll if I if I sell that
many you'll have to send me to the uh
Caribbean all expenses paid for 10 days
with a $100 meal allowance right guy
said there's no way you're going to sell
a million dollars worth of computers
it's not going to happen so I said oh
just okay he said he took the bet you
know so I go to work and I'm there like
three
days and he was right I I'm not very
good at sales so I hired a guy for 10
res owner and founder of bowai creative
we are a website development company uh
that donates free websites to
entrepreneurs with disabilities so yes
if you know anyone that um you know that
would be fit for the program please ask
them to get in contact with me my
website is WW .b creative.com so
folks welcome to the hustle Zone uh we
got we got a very special guest I've
been I've been begging this this this
gentleman for like decades for him to
Mentor me but because he's such a busy
entrepreneur he doesn't get the chance
so I'm going to see if we can uh after
this meeting that we're going to get
some dates so we can sit down and talk
or virtually sit down and talk but he's
he is a fantastic uh uh person um he's
into real estate you know he's he's a
techie like myself uh he has way more
experience than I do in in web
development and and programming and you
know video editing and all kinds of
things so I I I really want um you guys
the other thing too before we before I
introduce you to my guest I just want to
to say is that people have this idea
that entrepreneurs are
are motivational speakers in suits you
know that you know look like uh I don't
know I don't know what celebrity that
looks good cuz I don't really follow
that stuff but you know that look
good and a lot of us are not in suits
like myself if you if you see me out in
the streets you're not going to know
that I'm an entrepreneur when you see
Paul you're not going to know that he's
an
entrepreneur but he is is a really
successful entrepreneur and that's why I
I I like associating myself with with
guys like that you know and um he has a
lot I I I can't wait to have him on the
show because he has a lot to say and I'm
going to pick his brain as much as I can
so please welcome Paul Wall Hughes how's
it
going hey Ryan it's going great and
thanks for I don't know if I could live
up to that but I'll try and
uh you know I'm in Austin Texas you know
we if I I've got suits in that closet
back there but if I put a suit on and
went to any entrepreneurial meeting or
uh backro gathering in Austin they
they'd look at me like you're who are
you you know why why are you all dressed
up you know this is Austin Texas we
don't dress up there's in fact the norm
is dress down as much as possible Right
right and just like here in Calgary I
remember when I was young and I I I was
working for Xerox and you know a lot of
the I would wear my suit but a lot of
the guys would wear the golf shirts and
and whatnot because just it just in in
Calgary here it it wasn't necessary for
you to over overdress right and uh a lot
of people have a different everyone has
a different perspective of what an
entrepreneur is and a lot of the
motivational speakers and multi-level
marketing guys they come up and they
have they they kind of own that image or
they own that branding in terms of
business person but I I really want you
know when people watch the hustle Zone I
want them to see a wide variety of
people that you know some live really
basic lives but are very wealthy some of
them have exciting lives I know you have
an exciting life cuz every time when we
were on blab you know I I seen you you
you were in this place where you had
laser beams all over the
place and it was
out now you want I'm just
kidding but um you know so either way I
I thank you so much for for coming on to
the show and my the fans that watch The
Hustle Zone uh they get mad at me if
they if I didn't ask you this uh most
people uh the thing that separates
us is distance experience but you know
we have the one things that keep like
entrepreneurs connected is our habits
and uh the the first question I normally
ask my guests is what's your story like
where did you start how did you get to
where you are right now well it's a long
and winding road as as one
song says and uh it started out in uh I
guess at the University of Illinois
where uh when I went there in the late
60s we
were just starting to
learn about computers and Cad and
uh uh geographic information systems and
Architectural design with computers but
we were doing it with mainframes in the
early predecessors to the IBM weren't
even around them so uh it's it's been an
a long and Winding Road the the risk
here is that I'm I'm going to I'm going
to go too long so well this is what the
show is all
about what this is what the show is all
about we're here to hear your story it's
all about you so I'm I have all the time
in the world so from the University of
Illinois and where uh I was very lucky
to to get with some professors who were
pioneering in computer science because
my curriculum was urban planning I
learned how to do architectural drawings
I learned uh how to do social statistics
using computers and uh so on and we even
had like uh classes in flow charting you
know how to flowchart and design and
program so I was real lucky to get into
it early in the game and when I first
came to Austin Texas I actually got a
job with the very first software company
to go public and that's a trivia
question that probably no one will get
and when I when I landed there this was
like
this was unheard of to get a job in
software back then and this this company
designed all the accounting software for
the pre IBM PC Computers this were these
were the early stage predecessors before
the IBM came out and then IBM being also
right in Austin they they came over to
us and said hey we've got this new this
new computer and it runs something
called Doss and we were wondering if you
guys would help us with this you know so
we said yeah yeah we want to get on your
computer or on everybody else's computer
so we worked with IBN on on this thing
that nobody had heard of called Doss
right
Doss dis operating system and at that
time the dis was a was a uh either a
five and a quarter or three and a half
inch floppy disc you know that we're
we're not talking hard drives even it
was even before hard drives became
prevalent you know
and and so we this was very early on and
we had a lot of fun that was a fun
company and we were doing something that
nobody had heard of before and we were
having a good time we had a lot of
different colorful personalities running
around and uh you know Austin at the
time was kind of like a a hippie town
you know where you know you've heard of
uh you know the armadillo World
Headquarters and and uh you know asleep
at the wheel and all that they were it
was not a town known for Tech you know
but the BPI was the first company that
kind of ignited a tech Revolution and
now now we're off the charts I mean I
risked superlatives I risked Talking Too
Many superlatives if I talk about the
present day Austin Tech scene it's
phenomenal
[Music]
I'll use that one superlative and try to
limit
myself so when did you start to
um in in terms of the the the tech world
when did it start booming for you when
did you start you know seeing you know a
lot of this stuff come together and
you're like wow you know I'm part of a
revolution well you know I had a I had
probably the first computer in Austin
and I had the first I know I had the
first app 2 in Austin and I had the
first IBM PC in Austin and then uh I got
a job at computer sales you know and I
walked into this computer store and I
thought man I'll try computer sales you
know and that this was something very
different because I'd always been in
Tech and I had a very strong technical
background you know from working at BPI
and several other little startups and so
I walked into this computer store the
owner looks at me and he says
you might you're you're pretty good
technically but you're you're not going
to be able to sell computers come
on you don't look you're not a Salesman
I said well give me a chance he said he
said oh okay and I said here I'll make a
deal with you I if I sell this is a
store that probably sells maybe hundred
to
$150,000 worth of computers in a year
you know and I said I'll bet you I can
sell you a million dollars worth of
computers
this year and I and if I do I'll make
you a bet I I'll if I if I sell that
many you'll have to send me to the uh
Caribbean all expenses paid for 10 days
with a $100 meal allowance right the guy
said there's no way you're gonna sell a
million dollars worth of computers it's
not going to happen so I said oh just
okay he said he took the bet you know so
I go to work and I'm there like three
days and he was right I I'm not very
good at sales so I hired a guy for 10
bucks an hour to make phone calls right
he's making phone calls one after the
other I said just keep making them till
you get somebody that sounds like they
need a lot of computers you know that's
what I want I want a big I want a big
sale right so he kept calling and
calling about the 30th call he said
there's this guy on the phone his name's
Jay cash he's from a company that just
moved here from
California and I and I said well what
does he want he he said well the he he
has an order for 70 computers I said let
me talk to him right away grab the phone
you know and I didn't need that guy
after that day I went out to this
company it was called
semitech and uh I met with all these
Engineers from Motorola and IBM semitech
is a semiconductor Consortium made up of
like IBM Intel
AT&T uh Texas Instruments you know all
the the big semiconductor
companies in the country and the purpose
was to put throw everybody together and
trade ideas an unheard of concept in
capitalist America but this is what they
were doing so I went out there and said
look what's been going on you guys
what's happening I said well we just got
here from California and we need these
70 computers you know and I said great
I'll sayell you some compacts and I'll
sell you some ibms you know they're they
were selling going for like 10 to 12
each and these were like 386 at the time
I don't know if you even know what that
means
no they were three they were in 386
processor and they were huge they were
giant computers and Tower cases you know
and uh so man I wrote that order up that
order alone was like uh 70 grand you
know right there my first order so I was
on my way and uh the orders just kept
coming in and then they came to me and
they said well we're going to need some
support do you know somebody that could
give us tech support on all these
computers and I said well I'm your guy I
said uh I know all about tech and and
I've got a whole I know a whole bunch of
guys that will help me so I was getting
like I was getting like 120 an hour and
my assistants were making $70 an hour
and I was getting 25% of what they made
and uh and then I was getting uh
racking up orders around1 to $200,000 a
month some months we went up to three
and 400,000 so by the end of the year I
had I had had about three to five
somewhere between three and five million
in computer
sales so you which is unheard of I mean
that they they had never had numbers
like that in the store I mean the store
literally had Growing Pains trying to
keep up because they couldn't even they
had a hard time borrowing the money to
buy these to deliver them you know so
not only did I have to sell computers I
had to be a uh a broker for I had to
research uh lending institutions to
borrow money from to buy enough
computers to sell to these guys you know
because they were on net 30 right right
so anyway then to finish this off to
finish the story off I go into the
owner's off office at the end of the
year year and I said uh I said bill you
remember that deal we had don't you I
said he said what deal was that what
deal was that I said well you know I
gonna go to the Caribbean you know if I
sold enough computers and I I think I I
I not only sold a million dollars worth
I sold about three or four times that
you know and then I look down at his
desk you know what you know was laying
on his desk were two tickets to the
Cayman Islands for 10 days wow off I
went man to the Cayman Islands
wow forgotten all about our bet you know
but it just happened it just happened
because I had sold the most NEC
computers of anyone printers excuse me
most NEC printers of anyone that NEC had
sent him these two tickets right yeah
just coincidentally they were laying on
his desk you know I just happened to
notice them
that's amazing so uh what what made you
so successful in that situation I mean
uh a lot of people want to know how
could I sell that much luck had a lot to
do with it I mean I was at the right
place at the right time I had a positive
attitude but I just I just L you know I
locked into that call from you know for
from this uh you know from these uh
people at citech that was just lucky
pure luck you know so I can't take all
the credit for that it it was a matter
of timing and there's so many other
business opportunities where I wasn't at
the right place at the right time to
make up for it but there were a few
times where I was at the right place at
the right time you know and you kick
yourself for for what you could have
done but you just have to move on you
know right uh and and that's that's uh
that's a big big point that you're
making because I um even for
myself I could be lucky but it I'm lucky
because I'm always there I'm always
available I'm always ready you know I'm
you know I people know me that I'm
constantly grinding I I like I don't
even leave my house like this is where
this is where I work this is what I do
every day but you know in order for me
to catch those leads in order for me to
to to to see new opportunities I always
have to have my my ear on the ground and
you know so I think that we we can't
predict luck but we can predict really
good
habits absolutely yeah you do have to be
prepared and ready you know for the
opportunity and you have to recognize
the opportunity when it when it pops up
you have to create an environment where
where those kind of opportunities can
grow too you know where they can
incur and I think I provided a good
environment for that and uh
and it it and I worked for many many
startup companies in Austin I worked for
IBM in the user centered design for a
while I worked at
TI a lot of there were a lot of smaller
startup companies that I worked for I
worked for one of the uh first browser
companies too that that was actually
before uh you know before Netscape had
even taken hold and long before Google
Chrome you know and and all that so it
was interesting to work for a uh company
making a browser you know and that
browser no you've never heard of because
it never really took off it was called
Galaxy back then oh wow
Galaxy so now let's go let's dive back
before you know the tech days and you
know when you how how what was your
childhood like well I grew up in chiaka
Illinois which was a wonderful little
town that was uh situated between two
large Bluffs on the Mississippi River
and it was just a little tiny town but
they had it was like an engineered town
where they had uh had the focal point
was the children in the town where they
had bad mitt courts and and and uh
tennis courts and a big swimming pool
and and archery classes and fencing
classes and just all all summer long you
know there were this activities for kids
the kids had a play so it was a very
creative environment for children I wish
that uh our society would would think
more in terms of children supporting
children like that community did when I
grew up you know because I don't think
we're we're we're necessarily A child
Centric in this culture you know we
don't think too much about the the kids
and how important they are you know for
our
future right and um what about parenting
how was uh H how were you raised in
terms of
parenting uh my parents weren't real
strict they were they were uh pretty
lenient they let me get away with a lot
I never got in trouble except for once
or twice and uh then I ended up in High
School in h St Louis I I was a big into
sports into basketball and track mostly
and uh I still like sports I still like
Fitness activities I got recently got
the uh Nike watch I don't know if you
can see that yeah I can see
that you have to tap on it to make it
light up there it goes oh nice the Nike
watch which which tracks your activities
and tells you
just it tells you even to stand up and
get busy and when you go for a walk you
program it for a walk if you go for a
run you program it for run and now
they've even got the swimming you know
so I'm a real big fan of the current uh
craze for
Quantified uh Fitness you know
Quantified uh
tracking and um did your parents ever
know that um that you were going to be
as successful as you are
now uh I don't think so I think my mom
probably expected me to be highly
successful but not in quite the way that
I was more in a traditional business way
you know and uh my dad I'm not sure he
probably uh wanted me to succeed I don't
know if he had high as high expectations
for me as my Mom
though and um did you know did you even
have an idea that you know like when you
were young
that I mean you wouldn't have known what
you would have accomplished but you know
did you know that you were going to
succeed in something did you have an
Incarnation no I didn't I didn't have
any idea I wanted to when I was young
when I was a kid I wanted to be an
astronomer I had no clue you
know then I found out that there's a lot
of math to be an astronomer that there's
calculus and I decided Well maybe I
don't want to be an
[Laughter]
astronomer so now fast
forwarding you know you You' you've
you've developed some success around
technology and you get into real estate
can you tell us a little bit about the
real
estate well you know I I do a lot of
buying and selling and flipping with I
guess this the term they use a lot you
know condos and houses but my project my
big project is like a where I am now
it's 15 acre rural Village outside of
Austin and basically it provides lowcost
but high quality housing for people and
you know there's this this whole tiny
house movement we're part of that and we
also have vintage Airstream trailers and
then we built some very large houses
that people share and we build some
medium-sized houses that are duplexes
and then I build a built this house
which is 5,000 square feet for myself
whoa and uh and so it's quite developed
but at the same time uh it's a very
quiet peaceful environment where people
can have their peaceful enjoyment and uh
yet if they want to there's there's
people out here that are interesting to
talk to and get together with
everybody's
uh there we have people that are
Architects we have people that are movie
set designers we have
musicians we have uh some guy who's just
like a a hippie you know he just runs
around with Ros the hair and but he's
real helpful he helps everybody all the
time you know always there to help
people and then we have uh couple women
who are work in the Food Industries you
know and restaurant hotels and
restaurants and then for a while we had
a intern program where we brought in
people from the Philippines and they
stayed here and worked at a nearby
Resort in fact we at one point we had 18
Filipino young women and men staying
here 18 wow 18 yeah that's a lot of 14
women and four men they were all they're
either 20 or 21 years old and they were
all here on internships at this
hotel wow and when you what made you
think to do this to to to be a part of
this project um you know with with the
land and building these there wasn't a a
huge amount of conscious forethought or
planning you know and that's one thing
that I'm supposed to be good at is
planning but but this didn't come
together with a lot of conscious
planning it kind of grew organically it
grew well I think I'll build a house for
myself and then well I think I'll build
another house you know and rent it out
for people and then oh I guess I'll get
some Airstream trailers so I got about a
half a dozen Airstream trailers and fix
those up and it was just like uh there
was no master plan it was just grew inch
at a time you know yeah so you just kind
of grew over time and you know you seem
to be like just levelheaded you know
because I I I know I know people that
are like man I want Ferraris I want 10
million of them and you know they're out
there driving and you know but you seem
very calm I'm not sure how many like
cars you actually have and if you like
Ferraris uh but you know
what what tends to drive you in terms of
uh like yeah what what drives you in in
in
general you mean what kind of car do I
drive well no what drives you just like
what what sort of like do you have um
things that you that you that you like
that drives you to to want to be I don't
know um the thing that the thing that
drives me mostly is just it's not so
much so much money or wealth it's more
Health that drives me you know wanting
to be active and healthy and always
occupied and always doing something and
always moving you know being in motion
is important in fact we had a we had I
rented
uh the upstairs of one of our houses to
a couple Julie Angel and Vic berer and
they were they were really interesting
entrepreneurs because they were uh
promoting something called
move MN and which is short for movement
and nature and they would take people
out in the woods and uh teach them how
to survive and teach them how to climb
trees and and you know get through get
across creeks and just you know movement
in nature so we we have a really really
nice natural setting out here with this
big creek and yeah big big giant trees
and just just beautiful uh natural
setting so there's a lot of lot of uh
opportunity to go on walks and bike
rides and we have we've got a golf cart
path and it's it's real nice to be in a
a natural setting where you you don't
have to worry about cars you don't have
to worry about getting robbed or
anything or being out at night if you're
a woman you know it's just nice to be in
a comfortable setting you know around
other people who are friendly yeah I I
what I noticed about you um because I've
seen your I've I've seen a few things
that you've done in the past uh what I
noticed is that you are pretty active
like on your on your Google Plus I mean
it's hard to keep up with you you have
more exciting life than than than than
than I have in terms of your social
engagement and and whatnot but you're a
part of a lot do you I I see a lot of
pictures do you do photography I love
photography yeah and you know these new
new phones that they have now this this
Samsung 7 and the uh the uh this iPhone
7 yeah 7 plus what an awesome phone this
is you know yeah oh yeah that's a great
phone I love this phone and it takes
great photos you know it's got this
great H camera here it's just it's got
two cameras better than better than a a
DSLR no but uh I'm just talking
convenience and maybe you're you know I
don't know I don't know what the
percentage
of quality you get of a v i mean
obviously my Sony Alpha 7 is a better
camera than my phone camera right and uh
but look what it weighs look how big it
is and look how conspicuous I am using
it in like a public you know social
situation and I like to do a lot of
social photography and I don't want to
stand out as the photographer I don't
want people to look at me as he's the
photographer you know I don't want that
I just want to kind of blend into the
background and take pictures of
natural events as they occur you know
without influencing the picture yeah for
sure well that's that's amazing so we're
going to cut to Commercial and then
we'll be back to to wrap things up uh so
I I if you don't mind if you can put
yourself on mute for a about two minutes
and I'll key you back
in a web design company in Calgary is
taking the concept of helping others to
a whole new level and as Robin Crawford
reports it was an Okanagan man who
inspired them to use their Tech skills
to help people with
disabilities it gives me a great
pleasure to introduce to you Michael D
Haynes a motivational speaker an
entrepreneur and and a businessman
Michael Haynes is doing it all and I
absolutely love it it's the best job my
member had in the beginning Haynes
admits that he didn't know how to get
his customer service Consulting business
off the ground and then he met Ryan
Perez with bowai creative for every
website that we sell we donate uh free
websites to entrepreneurs with
disabilities the Calgary based company
builds websites for businesses Haynes
knew he needed a website to promote
himself and knew he had the tools to
help we were always talking about
working um um in the in or doing
something for the disability or for the
for people with disabilities um but we
didn't know what we were going to do and
I thought that this was a great time to
um to do something and and so we
invented this whole initiative like
pretty much around Michael bowai
creative built and maintains an entire
website for Haynes free of charge he
um put my ideas into
action and that made my my
job so much easier oh it's an initiative
that the four person company is proud of
it's especially close to pre's heart
because he himself has dyslexia I paved
my own path and that's why this this
this project means so much to me because
I want to help other people create their
path
bow TI creative is now helping other
people with mental and physical
challenges build websites across North
America all because of Michael Haynes
he's a great guy and it's fantastic
working with him and I can't wait to see
what happens next for him if you know um
anyone that has a mental or physical
disability that wants to become an
entrepreneur or you know needs to needs
help to get started in the right
direction definitely check out our
website haes hopes with the kind of
support offered by Perez and his team
more people will find the confidence to
reach their goals I have a challenge you
have a challenge there not a person
alive without a
challenge
I my challenge is more pronounced than
than yours Robin Crawford Global
News okay and we are back so um so we at
the second half of the hustle Zone and
um so I have a few we're going to change
the line of questioning here uh so the
first question I want to ask you if uh
uh if you don't
mind what what's your favorite
dessert um cherries and yogurt cherries
and
yogurt that's pretty simple dessert some
people say you know
uh cheesecake and whatnot but why why
cherries and and yogurt I don't know I
like cherries and I like I it's like the
combination I use some kind of custardy
type yogur my
wife feeds it to me a lot and I really
enjoy
it what what what makes you
happy uh being healthy makes me happy
and
uh being wealthy makes me happy wealthy
and healthy I have a friend that has a
uh business in Austin and she she calls
it healthy wealthy but the wealthy is w
l l t h y her actually her name is
wealthy wealthy it's wealthy like you'd
expect it and then wealthy W LL th h y
so being uh comfortable enough not to
worry too much and being healthy you
can't healthy health is and fitness and
uh feeling feeling good and being active
are things that uh are the most
important to me
right and um what what what's your
biggest pet
peeve oh gosh my biggest pet peeve is
people who hold grudges who never give
up their
grudges so you're exp why I mean why why
would you do that I mean my wife and I
get in a big argument it lasts one day
at the most at the max we don't carry a
grudge past that you
know and what what constitutes uh or
what what can you say to all those young
folks that are getting married what how
how do you keep a solid marriage
together don't be don't rush into it
make sure that it's the right marriage
because you don't want to have to keep
redoing it right
yeah most definit people a lot of people
have to read do this this because they
you know they have to hit the undo key
and then go into the set another cycle
you know so just take your time don't be
in a rush and try to get it right the
first time you know yeah what would you
give what advice would you give uh young
entrepreneurs that want to be
successful uh to try to try to expose
himself to to news and and uh read a lot
learn a lot and uh you know have the
right tools software tools apps and then
try to be on the Leading Edge try to be
a little bit ahead of the curve you know
like that's that a lot of My Success if
you call it success what I mean just you
know the fact that I was able to make a
good livelihood I don't want to get hung
up on this success thing yeah but uh
basically just I was always able to to
see what was coming next you know and
it's a little harder now that I'm 72
years old to see what's coming next
because I'm kind of retired now you know
but when I was when I was in the prime I
I was always a step ahead so you want to
try to get a step ahead figure out the
next the next thing that's coming along
right right and um last question if you
could look at your young younger self
what would you tell them I would tell
them to learn a lot more about
business and uh and focus on learning
business learning accounting learning
Finance learning uh marketing and sales
and uh just get a better so more solid
business background don't you know you
really have to think of uh what's going
to be important later on down the line
and
sometimes if you're just a pure
philosophy major or something it may not
cut it later on you know you may not
have the tools that you need you've got
to think about what tools you're going
to need and a lot of the most important
tools to be successful or knowing about
business and I I shorted myself in my
business training and knowledge when I
was younger I was more pure Tech rather
than than you know focus on the
the business I if I had to do it over
again I wouldn't have gotten a urban
planning computer science degree I would
have gotten an
MBA an MBA yeah an MBA with the focus
and Technical you know yeah yeah that's
amazing that's amazing Paul I really
enjoyed this conversation where can
people find you uh well uh I'm on Austin
spring.com
is my blog and my place where I hang out
if you want to hang out with me is
called Austin hangout.com and if you go
there nobody's there just
uh invite your invite me or don't invite
me or invite your friends and uh we can
chat some more if you want to carry on
this uh conversation some more that
we've started today yeah for sure and
what's Texas cowork.com
that's a company I started it was the
second I believe it was the second
co-working space in Austin after
conjuncture and uh it was a physical
co-working space that was right in the
heart of Austin right at six in Congress
which is uh what which is is the heart
of Austin it's like the part of it's the
center of
downtown and then I got bought out by my
partner then he fold because they raised
the rent and then he
died but now I have the name I have the
Texas co-working website and I'm using
that to kind of steer people to
different co-working spaces in the
Austin area and I've I'll have an
announcement in about a week I'm
starting a new
Venture with a partner in New York City
who's already been doing this in New
York City and what it is is it'll be a
co-working pass where if you have this
pass or this card you can go to any
co-working spot and in Austin we have
like 20 or 30 between 20 and 30
co-working spaces and I noticed that a
lot of people don't want to be at one
place all the time they like to jump
around and meet other people and yeah do
this so I'm working
on disseminating this co-working card in
Austin so that that you can co-work
wherever you want and if you happen to
travel to New York or San Francisco or
Toronto Toronto is one of them that
you'll have uh access to all the
co-working facilities uh wherever you go
well that's pretty cool so would you
come back onto the hustle Zone if you
once you're ready to launch I'd H I'd be
happy to have you back on so that you
can tell us more about it yeah yeah it's
kind of early I'm I'm just uh figuring
out how to do sales calls on this thing
right now but I'll get that figured out
and I'll get back with you yeah no
problem so uh did you enjoy your time in
the hustle Zone was it I did I you know
that I thought from the name you know I
thought we we were gonna have a sports
show I had no
idea and you you remind me you're the
spitting image of Mark Phillip a friend
of mine in Austin you got to see this
guy because you look you you guys look
exactly alike and he's he's an
entrepreneur you might want to talk to
because he's done a lot with uh Sports
and he has this thing called are you
watching this but anyway that's that
might be another good show for you down
the line yeah for sure for sure well
yeah well I appreciate you coming on and
um you know I would love to to to to
have more conversations with you my
friend so thank you so much for for um
um for coming into the hustle zone so
there's one last thing that I'm going to
ask you to do and if you haven't seen
the show that have you I'll let you know
here so I'm going to do a call and
response so I'm going to be like welcome
to the and then you're going to say
hustle Zone but you have to yell it out
you gota okay okay so welcome to the
hustle
Zone awesome thank you so much Paul I
really appreciate it this this was this
was